<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LibreOffice</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on LibreOffice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Donate</title><link>/donate.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/donate.html</guid><description>Donate To LibreOffice
Donation amount AED (card only) ANG (card only) ARS (card only) AUD AWG (card only) AZN (card only) BGN (card only) BOB (card only) BRL (card only) CAD CHF CLP (card only) CNY (card only) COP (card only) CZK DKK EGP (card only) EUR GBP HKD HRK (card only) HUF IDR (card only) ILS INR (card only) ISK (card only) JPY KES (card only) KRW (card only) KZT (card only) LTL (card only) LVL (card only) MAD (card only) MDL (card only) MKD (card only) MXN MYR (card only) NOK NZD PEN (card only) PHP PLN PYG (card only) QAR (card only) RON (card only) RSD (card only) RUB (card only) SAR (card only) SEK SGD SRD (card only) SYP (card only) THB TRY (card only) TWD UAH (card only) USD UYU (card only) VEF (card only) VER (card only) ZAR (card only) One time Monthly Quarterly Yearly Donate with Pay with Stripe Checkout LibreOffice is Free Software and is made available free of charge.</description></item><item><title>Download</title><link>/download.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/download.html</guid><description>Downloading for Business? Click here to learn more about long-term support, custom features, and more!
Learn more
Download LibreOffice
7.2.0
The latest version. If you&amp;rsquo;re a technology enthusiast, early adopter or power user, this version is for you!
Download 7.2.0 for Windows
32-bit detected. Download the 64-bit version. Download by torrent or see all mirror links.
Need another language?
7.1.5
This version is slightly older but more stable and has been tested longer.</description></item><item><title>For business</title><link>/for_business.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/for_business.html</guid><description>LibreOffice in business LibreOffice Community from The Document Foundation is great for home and small office users. TDF does not provide technical support for the software; users can get help from others on our mailing lists and Ask LibreOffice.
LibreOffice is also great for schools, educational and research institutions, and large organisations; in these cases, we strongly recommend using LibreOffice Enterprise versions from one of our ecosystem partners, such as those listed below.</description></item><item><title>Get help</title><link>/get_help.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/get_help.html</guid><description>Community Assistance Questions, answers, mailing lists, live chat and more
LibreOffice is created and maintained by its community. There are many ways you can find and access community assistance. If you are looking for professional support, please visit our dedicated page.
Ask.LibreOffice Have a question about LibreOffice? Get an answer here! This is the English version – some other Native Language Projects have Ask sites as well.
IRC (live chat) Join us on IRC at freenode.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>/imprint.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/imprint.html</guid><description>Imprint English Version Deutsche Fassung Imprint Responsible for the content of these pages is:
The Document Foundation
Kurfürstendamm 188
10707 Berlin
Germany
Please be advised that the contacts below DO NOT PROVIDE SUPPORT for LibreOffice – please do not send support requests. If you need help, we provide comprehensive documentation and user forums.
Phone: +49 30 55579920
Fax: +49 30 555799299
E-Mail: info@documentfoundation.org
Internet: https://www.documentfoundation.org
The Document Foundation is a charitable Foundation under German law (gemeinnützige rechtsfähige Stiftung des bürgerlichen Rechts).</description></item><item><title>Improve it</title><link>/improve_it.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/improve_it.html</guid><description>Get Involved Welcome! LibreOffice is developed by a friendly community, made up of hundreds of contributors around the world. It&amp;rsquo;s free and open source software, so anyone can study how it works and add improvements. Join us today and help us to make it even better! Check out the quick tasks below - or scroll further for more ways to help.
Before starting to contribute, it is recommended to schedule an orienting interview with TDF mentor Ilmari Lauhakangas.</description></item><item><title>LibreOffice timeline</title><link>/libreoffice_timeline.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/libreoffice_timeline.html</guid><description>LibreOffice Timeline Discover the history of LibreOffice and its predecessors! Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick summary – and then read on for the details&amp;hellip;
1985 Star-Writer I, written by Marco Börries, is released - initially for CP/M on the Amstrad CPC, and later ported to DOS
StarDivision is formed in Lüneburg, northern Germany
1991 StarWriter 5.5 is released, including StarWriter Compact 2.0 (shown below)
1992 StarOffice 1.0 is released, combining StarWriter, StarBase and StarDraw</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>/privacy_policy.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/privacy_policy.html</guid><description>Privacy Policy Datenschutzerklärung We provide an English translation of this policy for your convenience.
I.I Name und Anschrift des Verantwortlichen Der Verantwortliche im Sinne der Datenschutz-Grundverordnung und anderer nationaler Datenschutzgesetze der Mitgliedsstaaten sowie sonstiger datenschutzrechtlicher Bestimmungen ist die:
The Document Foundation (TDF)
gemeinnützige, rechtsfähige Stiftung des Bürgerlichen Rechts
Kurfürstendamm 188
10707 Berlin
Deutschland
Tel.: +49 30 55579920
E-Mail: info@documentfoundation.org
Website: https://www.documentfoundation.org
Link zum Impressum: https://www.documentfoundation.org/imprint I.II Allgemeines zur Datenverarbeitung 1.</description></item><item><title>System requirements</title><link>/system_requirements.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/system_requirements.html</guid><description>System Requirements Microsoft Windows Apple macOS (Mac OS X) GNU/Linux Android/Linux Other OSes
Microsoft Windows The software and hardware prerequisites for installing LibreOffice on a Windows system are as follows:
Microsoft Windows 7 SP1, Windows 8, Windows Server 2012, or Windows 10 Pentium-compatible PC (Pentium III, Athlon or more-recent system recommended) 256 MB RAM (512 MB RAM recommended) Up to 1.5 GB available hard disk space 1024x768 resolution (higher resolution recommended), with at least 256 colors Administrator rights are needed for the installation process.</description></item><item><title>Who are we?</title><link>/who_are_we.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:52:06 +0300</pubDate><guid>/who_are_we.html</guid><description>Who are we? LibreOffice is community-driven and developed software, and is a project of the not-for-profit organization, The Document Foundation. LibreOffice is free and open source software, originally based on OpenOffice.org (commonly known as OpenOffice), and is the most actively developed OpenOffice.org successor project.
LibreOffice is developed by users who, just like you, believe in the principles of Free Software and in sharing their work with the world in non-restrictive ways.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>/security.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/security.html</guid><description>Security If you came here looking for end-user support, please send any questions not related to a specific security bug to users@global.libreoffice.org.
The security teams for products associated with the codebase can be contacted at officesecurity@lists.freedesktop.org - this includes representatives of many vendors, and associated projects. This email address is solely for reporting security issues related to the software. If your virus checker is flagging a LibreOffice download as containing a virus, this is almost certainly a false positive.</description></item></channel></rss>